Overview
RESTful API setup.
API code automatic generation.
Supports microservices and models (built-in models).
Database integration via Database connectors. 
Inability to search through tables and cohesive models of data.(solution -  Views/Sequalize )
Built-in API explorer module and API documentation (Swagger).
Built-in ORM/ODM.
Built-in access-level controls.
File upload libraries.
Mobile client SDKs for Android, iOS, and Angular.js.
Can auto-generate an AngularJS services.
